winpalace.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy - WinPalace Casino - Best Online Casino Games, Casino Bonus Cash, Slots

## Introduction

**WinPalace Casino** (the "Company" or "we") offers gambling services. When you use the Company's gambling services, and whether such use is via the Internet Platform or an Alternative Platform, you shall be asked to provide personal information ("PI") to the Company. You should read this Privacy Policy in conjunction with the  WinPalace Casino Terms and Conditions. 

## Collecting Personal Information

We collect PI when you register and use our gambling services, make customer inquiries, register for information or other services from the Company, or when you respond to communications from us (such as questionnaires, emails or surveys). The PI we will collect from you may include, for example, your name, email address, home address, telephone number, debit/credit card data and date of birth and other information collected on registration or through surveys which the Company shall undertake. Our web site as well as our advertising system automatically logs Internet IP addresses accessing our site.

## How Your Personal Information is Processed ("Purposes")

The PI which you provide to us will be processed for one or more of the following Purposes: (i) to allow us to provide you with gambling services; (ii) to process any of your requests for information; (iii) to provide member support services to you; (iv) to market our services or products or those of other entities existing within the same group of companies in which the Company exists ("WinPalace Casino"); (v) to notify you about updates to our software and/or services; and (vi) to support any of the intended purposes specifically stated at the time at which you provided the PI. 

## To Whom Your Personal Information is Disclosed ("Recipients")

We ensure that your information will not be disclosed to government institutions or authorities except if required by law. E-mail Addresses are NOT shared with any other organization for commercial or non-commercial purposes. E-mail addresses will only be used to provide our customers with information regarding new software updates, promotional material, and miscellaneous casino operations, such as deposits and withdrawals. Your PI may, for the Purposes, be disclosed for processing to any of the following Recipients: (i) to any companies within  WinPalace Casino and their employees who have a need to know such information; (ii) to any third parties which provide services to the Company in order to allow or enable us to provide you with gambling services, including, by way of example, payment processors and data verifiers; (iii) to any third parties who provide Win Palace Casino services in relation to the operation of all WinPalace Casinos properties; (iv) to any auditors, contractors or other advisers auditing any of WinPalace Casino's business processes; and (v) to any potential purchasers or investors in any company within WinPalace Casino. Any processing performed by any Recipients will, where required by law, be governed by a data processing agreement in the form required by law, preserving any and all of your statutory data protection rights and obligating the Recipients to respect the PI and handle it in accordance with the relevant laws. 

## Emailing

Out of respect for your right to privacy we are happy to provide you with an easy means to decline receiving email offers from us. At any time, you may request to discontinue receiving these offers by sending a blank message with the word "Remove" in the subject area to [**support@winpalace.com**](mailto:support@winpalace.com).

## Security

We have implemented suitable security policies, rules and technical measures to protect and safeguard the entire PI under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All our employees and data processors that have access to, and are associated with the processing of your PI, are obliged to respect your privacy.

## Cookies

We may send you a permanent cookie when you register with us. A cookie is a small file that can be placed on your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can help us to recognize you when you next visit our website, note the advertisements you click on and the other sites you enter via a link from our website. This allows us to tailor the service we provide to your preferences. We may also use the data generated from cookies to compile statistical data on your use of our website. You are not obliged to accept a cookie from us or from any other website. You can modify your browser so that it will not accept cookies. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for instructions on how to do so correctly. However, for legitimate security reasons, we may refuse access to specific website content unless you accept the use of a cookie or similar device

## Protection of Minors

The services provided by the Company are not intended for or directed to minors or persons under the age of legal consent. Any person who provides us with PI represents to us that they are of legal age or in their jurisdiction. We reserve the right to access and verify any PI submitted by or collected from you. If we become aware that a minor has attempted to, or has submitted PI, we may not accept this information and may take steps to remove such information from our records. 

## Retention

Your PI will not be stored for any longer period than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected. This Privacy Policy is subject to change, so please check it regularly. We reserve the right to amend or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and in response to changes in applicable data protection and privacy legislation. In the event the Purposes change, we will notify you as soon as possible and, where required seek your consent where such notification relates to a new additional purpose for processing.

If you have any enquiry about this Privacy Policy please write to [ support@winpalace.com](mailto:support@winpalace.com)
